Now, if I'll lower the register to the council,
the council gets to the remainder of the set,
I'll be 22.
Two, the population is learning the honorary,
the second half of the staff of the mainstream,
the majority of the numbers, the numbers,
the teams, the groups, the drivers.
Can they come up with your proof?
The second.
The staff.
Don't go.
Sonberg.
Davis.
Parker.
Hi.
And the groups to make sure to get a welcome us on purpose.
You have to get the wedding.
That's what I'm looking for.
Everybody's five and six.
So, let's take a look.
Davis.
Hi.
Sonberg.
He's set.
Parker.
Hi.
He's set.
Parker.
Hi.
He's set.
He's.
He's coming up.
born in a thousand.
He's off stretcher.
He's set.
It's gone.
He's cute.
白.
And we're supposed to sort this story.
There's night.
I think that's something to do.
Since then, I've been heard like with Supreme Court, we've had a
couple of nominations, and I can just stand down to the minimum.
Why haven't had a business?
And you can see it like it's a normal time back to the wrong generation.
And then one of that part of the case is primary and back up for a
We're a great convent rescue help done that even a lot from the 80s and 90s and we're going to up.
And to take any points for the action on the real racing and take one, there you go.
We have to have this to protect our office, our office, and totally sing along and we don't have this commitment.
So it's a great virtue for us to do this and great work with the qualified tribe.
And there's one of the things that we have that.
The questions for Chief on that.
We definitely need to bring the home portion of our cell by a lot of issues by not having a cross death with the regular tribe.
Because if we're involved in any kind of a safe, one more officer would be there with four of us to help all of us.
And there's a shooting there of what ever we're going to make both.
I mean it's going to make both.
We're going to go back and go out to the voice library.
That sounds so.
So in the end, staff.
I mean, the mayor has really put a funding on all of those for role enforcement.
And now, I think, most of all, our officers got, like, our six commission.
We weren't even in this exact same thing with the situation.
We're all the problems outside part of the town.
We're succincting this.
There's going to be a couple more.
Once that are.
Try the rule on.
Of course.
I believe we'll be proud of them with all those.
All we would like to have.
I'm just a special.
Of course.
But that's always the way to be able to be able to be able to be able to be able to.
But until that's for them, we have to go in the room.
We're going to go in the room.
You might have any questions.
I'll make a motion to approve.
Second.
Part.
Some people.
Some work.
Part.
Thank you.
Hey.
And here's my next one.
You.
So Mr. Baker, here's the council.
During our budget setting process last summer, this is one of the things that I mentioned.
We should start doing this at St. John Council, which is a big review.
And it's simply just an overview.
And I love what to give citizens, the division, transparency, and where we're actually.
As well as the council members, the ability to see how we need more expectation regarding revenue and expenses.
And so the one thing that we're dealing with and walks us through is some of these kinds of guidelines.
I said we want to point out that when we look at this first item up there, we've got our state general fund.
In under the review side, you'll see that we've got a percent collective, about 65.4%.
This is very good.
This is obviously a positive in the United States, very good.
But to look at that in context, we've divided this past fiscal year, expected revenues in around 6.8 million.
It dissipated, we collected by the end of this fiscal year, which we end of June.
Today we collected around 4 million.
So we're still about 2.8 million.
We are expected to run this for the year, but we still have an additional six months to go.
In some of the year, we are definitely on target.
I certainly don't sleep well at night until we've been at our 6.8 million since that's what the project was based on.
But we do anticipate that by the end of this fiscal year if things continue to trade the way we are,
then we will be certainly in good financial standards.
You know, overall, we look at this as a 15.42 percent above the project overall revenues in about 9.9 percent above our project itself.
So here these are good numbers.
We continue to see how things trend in the end of the year.
But what that being said, the rest of this argument in what Joe's going to watch you through is,
we went through and really discussed things that we thought were material and significance in high-lighted bill,
because you're yellowed that.
And so at this time, it feels going to kind of walk through some of those that we thought were of significance
and then discuss and answer any questions.
You can come to the end of the year.
So I could say one day, just go to the end of the year.
And we have to think that we've got a pretty good attention.
You already discussed the general level.
So we have 29% that decision, 29, small rules, specificity plan.
Our two largest are Joe Fund, which is the number of four ones.
And then image array is the number that actually is the largest one.
I'm just going to hear what I'm going to say one is exposed to the one first to the third June.
So I'm not going to talk about the sales tax.
Unless you may question a lot as a question that the entity has.
But it is looking good so far.
Thanks.
We haven't been looking great so far.
If you go down to the next, to fund 1 to 20,
where there's going to be a 39 or 41%.
That is high line.
So most of our guys are actually going to have lots.
And the format comes in.
That's 12 of the months.
We get a 12th of our revenue.
And we spend a 12th of our revenue.
Which month of all year.
And I do not agree on this like that.
Sometimes I spend it all the first year in the year.
There's different things.
And we'll point those out.
We just got to go on here at the point now.
Fun point 20 is one of those.
So inside of that fund.
You give us our key.
That's the minus number of refrigeration programs.
And the CDV program.
That's chip.
I've given it in this turn.
It shows the revenue.
39.41.
The end day.
Or not one of those times.
It comes in.
A little bit every month.
They are.
They have a call.
They're always using that.
I guess.
When it's nice, they're making money.
And it's not, there's not red, you know, all those red ones are on the red side.
So that's how we're on the red.
They're the red, you're right by seeing what they don't have to do with the road.
Do you want to say anything to them?
The other fun, the next fun is CDB fun, the real two.
Their red news are at 63.96 percent, that is Delta X, and the left-handlet
state to that issue.
I think the biggest thing is the point out, because I'm going to get a bit of a
majorism that makes you guys, and we talk a lot about some trends that we were seeing
here in Northeastern, but we were looking a little bit higher, and then some of the other
large, much of areas.
A lot of that is a major travel, artsy, and the CDB we also track in-bound, traffic, and the
church I guess.
And we've seen it in the last, really, about 90 days, there's been a substantial gain in people
exiting, turning from the dirt to the big one for us, with numbers going from one so a lot of
people come from that, such a lot of areas that are exiting at Miami, and that's our hope
is that, when they do that, those are some of the increase that we're seeing, if I'm telling
us, but a lot of it is leisure.
I think we shared a lot of time, one of the things that we had done, and that's very aggressive,
kind of a re-opening plan, when we were sat down, I mean we had about eight months there that
we just kind of, and we were doing good in that table, so we really didn't spend anything.
Just because we were trying to make sure everybody had a paycheck because everything could just
stop, so we came out on the other end of that, we didn't have a pretty aggressive campaign,
and we've been out, and we were allowed to really market in front of the city going in, so I think
that is a little bit of a really overall leisure travel right now, with a rubber tie, and we got
a little bit of church in front of a couple months ago with the Poland, and we learned about
some of the 90 months or some of the Americans, and the travel on the next month, and we've learned
one and that was a statistic that was put out by the long run, so I think that it's probably not
going to be on the other end of the time, we still are being extremely conservative, we haven't
spent a lot of money, like Gils that are there, our biggest spend are ahead of us, so we've got a
spring campaign, it was 16 campaign, we're getting very sure around, and I can tell you it's a trip
a lot of love, we've always been able to do the cows, because we just kind of had that budget for
a thousand feet to be able to have that strong campaign, we've got a couple more billboards
coming up, very good in social media, so then as you know, we're very, very kind of, we go campaign
that we use our campaign on the city, so we're normally around 16, maybe at the time, we're getting
very full launch 9 this spring, because I don't, we'll keep it out, we'll see those, our
revenues are out, and our expenses are down right now, like I said, between now and probably
also middle of May, just the amount of expenses and the good, good scams, so we're putting
those extra dollars to really be able to promote some of the city in the way we're going to be
just like a stranger, and I'm kind of not trying to stand out about that, which we hope people
be trying on.
I'd say no.
I'd like to.
Good question.
So the next time we point it out, because we initiated a federal law, and just kind of
that's already new to it.
The red leaves are 56, 56% per cent.
A big part of that is there's two people.
One, we do budget because our delivery is we never want it over budget already, so
and I would spend that budget and not get the red leaves when people were budgeted.
That way.
The other thing is, GRD has changed the way that they build us.
So here's a error for ever.
We had a thing that the EPA has purchased power adjustment from GRD, and I'm on the invoice.
They said that has to purchase out.
Probably.
They stopped that.
They changed the way they did.
They did their.
They're.
They're right.
System.
And that EPA would like.
I think it may be.
Maybe.
Last year.
I mean, I had.
I had.
That came back into existence.
So a PDA.
Once we get it.
It's called.
PDA to us.
To the city.
But when it's.
It's.
And.
That.
So it's.
It's.
Thoughting.
We can.
You know that.
It's. Now.
And that also, a transfer from an instrument as to that.
That transfer from an instrument started when the citizens
afforded to be extremely, so it's expected to come in and the council
had a transfer from 5,000 to a million within a year
where we were at a bunch of wise into that time to stand on over here.
Right now, when the expenditures were $1.85,
I want to point that out, and this is a fun that also got some
quality of the city in the high season, and it's going to be a little
close, just like turquoise.
So I know they've spent an $1,000 in that was I'm sure
to say, and then we'd be right around $1,000 in five, two, one.
Yeah, so on the Regan Cirque Streets, it's about $100,000 in
the loft.
If you want to remind me of this, don't be mad at us, don't be mad.
If you know we went, we're estimating, I'd love that to be one of these right now from somewhere in the Toronto Valley, the sea street.
So that would be about a million years.
So I don't think we're out of the net.
You know, I've been standing on 150,000 for the three, four, one of them in the church at the time.
And also the one that we have to work for the road to the sea.
We've been building up our right to the road.
We have about 100,000 about the budget of the street.
We've been working for these to go from.
We did these to the zone.
To these three there were kinds of concrete.
So that one they're going to, you know, take what we're going to do.
So that has to happen.
So that would be awesome.
I'm going to also have the one that's going to be starting to bring it back on.
And they're up and down.
And we started to have the other.
And we got a few times on this.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
So we kind of, you know, when they're all in their day or three,
they don't have to come in to the concrete.
Just like there's a sidewalk here.
It's got a way of the name, you know, I think it's got a concrete.
I'm going to let you find the good day.
I've been building up my right to the.
You know, it's you.
But I don't know if it's like just that kind of a little bit of the need to be.
You kind of hear it.
And I have to just bring the all the stuff.
You know, that question about that.
The next one.
You know, because we have to put this on the.
We just want to point out that.
This year, we gave everyone to go and have to start two and a half out of three.
That's one of the years started, and I was just going to start it.
57% of those money's haven't spent, but I think we know we wouldn't have to do it.
It's hard to get things, so we're just pointing out that it's difficult.
And things are out of the year or more.
So they're really, really, it's a thing that that's just something we can have.
It's a struggle to get the truck.
I don't know what they mean.
The next one we want to talk about is the airport fund.
So right now, they're a school teacher.
They're a 90% of the 6% of that.
So I'm really crazy, but this is another one that they have a reason.
They get big grants.
And they're very personal grants.
So they have to spend it.
And once they finish the project, we need to give it a burst.
And sometimes, you know, we're just doing that value right now on that.
I don't know if they're still on some of them all over.
So, we've done a lot of grants.
And they think they're a mathematical grant.
They've just so much money in their way to see.
And to do our math and math.
We've done almost normally an article that we've produced here.
We've organized a taxiway.
We've heard of his paint.
And we've ridden a real life.
We've heard a lot of infrastructure to come in there.
But tomorrow, math part has...
I don't know where we'll go right now, and a lot of things to do with the question I said.
But the majority is that it's just infrastructure barriers with the law.
It's proven it's over the last few years to, it's proven here for working in a project,
and I don't know if we can really come around and bring a lot of relevant entities.
What are we going to say?
We're going to talk a little bit about the question I'm going to answer.
So how do you want to demolish your account on the talk about that?
That is what we're dealing with properties.
And I don't know if Christy wants to talk about that on the demo fund.
Yeah.
I'll just want to talk about what that fund is and where we're at with using those funds to do some of this information.
So we just got done finishing an RQ, that was about almost $70,000.
I think that's the way to work out getting the human grant of the knowing and just that the assessor's testimony.
That's one of the properties, three of those other people.
A commercial, a larger, a commercial database in that, that's got to set capacity right now.
We just had property here in some protein properties.
And we're getting ready to put those in the paper.
We had more than $4,000 that was in Shala for them.
So back and then my time is just, in my point, I'm going to put a lot of little bit.
Probably, we're going to be actually going down 10 of those.
Two million dollars out of the problem.
In the next six months.
Yeah.
So that is a lot.
That would be our solid waste facility and the number of contractors, you know, typically, there are a lot of contractors that they don't have work.
So it would be a challenge to get all that done.
I don't need to do a statement for the assessors.
And there's only that that's going to work.
Our facility.
That would help do assessors.
So we have that out.
Yeah.
How many of you have done these right now for them all?
For them all will be, so the 14 that would just have the property here.
So what happens?
We have to have, we find the properties and we have to have the property here in the bush.
And then we have to go through a process of trying to find the worst of these properties.
And then during the time, they may come in and say, we're not going to face this up.
And thank you for your comment and we target those six notes.
So either it's an effort, it's an effort, it's an effort, it's an effort, it's an effort and one is to be
super taking someone's property with the money. So we've got it. It's a weekly process.
There's about 30 on the list that we need to have proper hearings.
Like, I can just have 14, but to the close-out process.
I may have a little bit of bloodline.
But 14, we just have to just have those probably about five of them.
So the 11, or two, is nine, they're black.
Why happens to those who just have a minute to talk to?
I think they're interested in your question.
The nine of the black ones, because what's the one that they're not put on?
Oh.
I don't know what to talk about.
So we're waiting on the Sunday on feedback about the consolidation of our boards, the C boards,
and admissions.
What we'd like to do is put in a program where these properties are transferred to the
library, within the city, and then a program started to have this as incentive to get people started to build it.
But we want to get it in the right.
When it, the city can't get that property away.
We need to get it to one of our boards and have our authority back to the board of work on it.
So the process is so long because of statute, or what it does, or what it does.
State statute.
State statute are permitting process.
A lot of people will sit on their property until we have a community for property curing.
And then their next go-to is, well, if that's the body of my interest in buying this.
So then we've got to kind of look at, oh, to see if something happens.
And we have to go six months that's how long you don't know for that is poor.
And then you have to, if they don't sell it, and between that time period, you've got to go back to the
business that won't process.
And we try to make sure that we follow a very new town, because we take it to my property.
So the taxpayer and all that we're out, was there anyway, like that?
Well, that's what we several months ago.
And then I came to the council and talked to you guys about assuming the property owner or that money.
So that's not something that's done in the past, but we've figured out a way to deal with the county.
And if we file a name on a property for those costs, and the county determines that that meaning is uncollectable,
then we added this to the door for us to actually save the property owner and civil court to get those money back.
So yes.
In the past, we were just out of taxpayer money.
We're fine with the pain.
Thank you.
As it stands right now, then 22 potentially.
Good big end up this year.
This year.
Thank you.
Which is a business.
There's a lot.
And that's going to be really good.
I'm going to contact this.
We did it on what they did.
We did that work.
So what's the total number?
How does it are going to be?
So I don't have a total commitment.
Most of the properties that are in property here in this.
So the 20 plus properties that are still written on them.
That is those are typically can daily properties.
That we can do.
That's how the process kind of gets started.
Not all of those are given in mode, you know, just depends.
And I don't know if I don't have that in the group.
So I can get it.
I'll send it to you.
So these are the properties that we didn't have on those as well.
Or if you don't have it.
Yes.
Any property that's done through the field of grant, the acquisition grant, that property has to remain
a developer in the green space.
And I'm starting to read and I can't give it back.
The properties that were by the paragraphs or something as it looked at,
and the parking lot, the parking lot, the parking lot by the paragraphs and the feedback.
So the ones that are using grant are all of the way.
Thank you.
Any time.
Any questions?
Not in court of the 20, 20, 22 back to zero two.
And then in section 24, that's under three.
The introduction of services and players playing this connection.
It's a final build.
I don't know.
So the mayor.
And the next.
This.
The.
.
It's.
The.
If.
You.
It's a point for their A31 question.
This is the result of the conversation.
We had that meeting.
So there are the questions on the slide.
It's not understanding clearly what you were saying.
But this is what I understood.
It's the direction.
You have the straight up copy as well as you have a red line copy.
I think the big question that you all have was at what time does it piece?
This can be a question that I can give you.
When is it our trucks are on the property?
Or is it definitely on this?
Wasn't that the point?
If I remember correctly, we were trying to define what one of the key.
Yes.
So if you read line copy says that the V is end to the account,
where the utility truck arrives at the account.
Add this.
I'll make a motion.
Excuse me.
Marker.
Mark.
ulo Michael.
Marker.
Gabriel.
It.
Valerie.
Prosecutors.
It.
and executive session, the last thing, basically, the same
coordinates that you looked at at that time, because I did not hear
that, and many, many, many changes to it. Other than, I didn't make it.
I found a couple of typos, typos, essentially it's the same
coordinates that you looked at at that time.
part of the way that we think of this way, why don't we send it in place?
I don't think we're rude.
Second.
Parker?
I don't know.
I don't.
But first.
Famous.
All right.
Except.
11.
12.
13.
So, many of you could remember some cancel there were about a couple of things I wanted to talk about first off was.
I wanted to mention my last week with the recording weather that we had.
Due to that weather, we did have office closures of the first day in the Friday and last week.
And really, it's simply one of them, you know,
a first off of a shake staff, and their ability
to respond to the rally and the occasion.
And I'm very grateful now to the snow days today,
or not the snow days, but the yesterday.
It's not really just closing off as everybody goes home
and then happens.
It actually generates quite the opposite
of the programming board work that we actually
have, such a ability today to tell them
that the ability to run the majority of our services
with staff outside using our technology,
using the laptops, the remote access,
the Microsoft 365, that we have
the ability to run the majority of the services.
Obviously, we have a central personnel that are out,
performing live safety services,
these environments, community assisting people
have needed.
But the office work that generally happens in the office
when we close on such a day, we've got great capacity
today to even run our customer service,
just minus the walk-up window.
They still take calls, they still take emails,
they still have the ability to remote in,
and perform services.
If someone calls and needs something done, they can claim it.
We also have the online services today.
We have it out.
We have the same capacity.
We have the advanced functionality,
but people can go online.
You can record there.
You can also pay off the phone.
We also have Kevin and his group.
the ability to connect with this kind of church as if someone was, specifically in the case of whether or not that's
that's, I mean, is having an anticipated sort of set in the utility term known, you know, perhaps taking
the work for protection of building from three to two temperatures.
We have a process of place where somebody contacted us from the operations center.
We can coordinate with that citizen and Kevin, the visiting was fully prepared to go out
right away whether it would be able to search its turn on.
Things went really smoothly.
I hope your experience was the same that you all did receive calls that you did.
I'm quite interested in helping me back.
It really was a good opportunity for us to give even more practice with our technology and functionality.
On the third day of the Friday snow day, which probably is a little less stringuous than
maybe an actual weather event would be attached to things that hit our town where we actually need it to use
our universal situation.
Save a loss of this building.
This gave us even more experience and ability to figure out where things are and what we do well and what we need to do better.
So, again, you all have a feedback from those events.
The last time I wanted to mention was my work.
We have a play, we're on the worried express that it's going to be in the Column Theatre.
And we're going to be in the fourth and the 26th, 7pm.
And again, if that we're in 27, 2pm.
And our own key thoughts work is our idea of our work.
We'll be in that play.
He plays the role of Samuel Rager.
And we also have Jesse Black, who is the CVB.
And I hope I get this right because you're looking at him.
But Jesse will be playing the role of Colonel Artethon.
I think I'm going to have to keep track of that.
Anyway, really proud of him.
And I'm going to take him to the pride of our community and just begging him this little dear.
So, anybody may be down in New York City.
And I think we can be a great play on myself and decide to keep changing things.
With that, I want to make any questions.
I got to say that we've been talking about the service that I didn't get involved with.
We're going to welcome the United States.
But I don't know what the business office is called.
I don't know what the business office is called.
So I have a message.
So I get that information on what we do.
Well, I'm a GALA of the self-manager.
And I'm counting on it immediately.
I got a message, right now, some Saturday.
GALA just wants me on Saturday.
I'll go to the ball.
And then today we have a Industry customer.
Thank you.
It was very good.
Like here.
I got it.
This is my opinion, my first question.
that is also a great, she's been great job, she knows the customers' service, she handle
our customers.
That's totally different way and we're a small one.
And I'm extremely happy because I'm getting a clear call with us.
I think if you're part of the school that she needs, you didn't hear me.
We just gave her a big deal of this thing.
We won't be called the chief of land.
So I'd like to thank you for sharing that.
We don't shoot as a famous hire.
We didn't have a great job.
We don't have a great job.
We don't have a lot of things to do.
Perfect.
I want to give her a few.
She does.
Thank you.
Next, we'll give her a few.
Someone.
Second.
Someone?
Pardon?
Please.
All right.
Sender?
Excuse me.